<?xml version="1.0"?>
<library>
	<!-- Best Movie ever -->
	<Movie id="The Revenant">
		<title>The Revenant</title>
		<regie>Alejandro G. Iñárritu</regie>
		<year>2015</year>
		<url>resources/movies/revenant.jpg</url>
		<producer>Alejandro G. Iñárritu</producer>
		<music>Robert Lopez, Kristen Anderson-Lopez, Christophe Beck</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
            In late 2011, Hugh Glass guides Captain Andrew Henry's trappers through unorganized territory. While he and his half-Pawnee son, Hawk, are hunting, the company's camp is attacked by an Arikara war party seeking to recover their Chief's abducted daughter,
			Powaqa. Many of the trappers are killed during the fight, while the rest escape onto a boat. Guided by Glass,
			the survivors travel on foot to Fort Kiowa, as he believes traveling downriver will make them vulnerable. After docking, the crew stashes the pelts near the shore.
			While scouting game, Glass is attacked by a grizzly bear and left near death. Trapper John Fitzgerald, fearful of another Arikara attack, argues that the group must mercy-kill Glass and keep moving.
			Henry agrees, but is unable to pull the trigger; instead, he offers money for someone to stay with Glass and bury him after his death.
			When the only volunteers are Hawk and the young Jim Bridger, Fitzgerald agrees to stay for money, to recoup his losses from the abandoned pelts.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Interstellar">
		<title>Interstellar</title>
		<regie>Christopher Nolan</regie>
		<year>2014</year>
		<url>resources/movies/interstellar.jpg</url>
		<producer>Paramount Pictures</producer>
		<music>Hans Zimmer</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			n the mid-21st century, crop blights and dust storms threaten humanity's survival.
			Corn is the last viable crop. The world has also regressed into a post-truth society where younger generations are taught ideas such as the Apollo moon missions were faked.
			Widowed engineer and former NASA pilot Joseph Cooper is now a farmer. Living with him are his father-in-law, Donald; his 15-year-old son, Tom; and 10-year-old daughter, Murphy. After a dust storm, strange patterns made from dust inexplicably appear on Murphy's bedroom floor, she attributes the anomaly to a ghost. Cooper eventually deduces the patterns were caused by gravity variations and are a binary code for geographic coordinates. Cooper follows the coordinates to a secret NASA facility headed by Professor John Brand, Cooper's former supervisor. Professor Brand says gravitational anomalies have happened elsewhere. 48 years earlier, unknown beings positioned a wormhole near Saturn, opening a path to a distant galaxy with twelve potentially habitable worlds located near a black hole named Gargantua. Twelve volunteers traveled through the wormhole to individually survey the planets. Astronauts Miller, Edmunds, and Mann reported positive results. Based on their data, Professor Brand conceived two plans to ensure humanity's survival. Plan A involves developing a gravitational propulsion theory to propel a mass exodus, while Plan B involves launching the Endurance spacecraft carrying 5,000 frozen human embryos to colonize a habitable planet.
			
			Cooper is recruited to pilot the Endurance. The crew includes scientists Dr. Amelia Brand (Professor Brand's daughter),
			Dr. Romilly, Dr. Doyle, and robots TARS and CASE. Before leaving, Cooper gives a distraught Murphy his wristwatch to compare their relative time for when he returns. After traversing the wormhole, Romilly studies the black hole while Cooper, Doyle, and Brand descend in a landing craft to investigate Miller's planet, an ocean world. After finding wreckage from Miller's ship, a gigantic tidal wave kills Doyle and delays the lander's departure. Due to the proximity of the black hole, time is severely dilated. As a result, 23 years have elapsed for Romilly on Endurance by the time Cooper and Brand return.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Avatar">
        <title>Avatar</title>
		<regie>James Cameron</regie>
		<year>2009</year>
		<url>resources/movies/avatar.jpg</url>
		<producer>James Cameron</producer>
		<music>James Horner</music>
		<runtime>161</runtime>
		<plot>
			In 2154, humans have depleted Earth's natural resources, leading to a severe energy crisis. The Resources Development Administration (RDA for short) mines for a valuable mineral — unobtanium — on Pandora, a densely forested habitable moon orbiting the gas giant Polyphemus in the Alpha Centauri star system.[10] Pandora, whose atmosphere is poisonous to humans, is inhabited by the Na'vi, a species of 10-foot tall (3.0 m), blue-skinned, sapient humanoids[34] that live in harmony with nature and worship a mother goddess named Eywa.
			To explore Pandora's biosphere, scientists use Na'vi-human hybrids called "avatars", operated by genetically matched humans; Jake Sully, a paraplegic former Marine, replaces his deceased identical twin brother as an operator of one. Dr. Grace Augustine, head of the Avatar Program, considers Sully an inadequate replacement but accepts his assignment as a bodyguard. While escorting the avatars of Grace and fellow scientist Dr. Norm Spellman as they collect biological data, Jake's avatar is attacked by a thanator and flees into the forest, where he is rescued by Neytiri, a female Na'vi. Witnessing an auspicious sign, she takes him to her clan, whereupon Neytiri's mother Mo'at, the clan's spiritual leader, orders her daughter to initiate Jake into their society.
			Colonel Miles Quaritch, head of RDA's private security force, promises Jake that the company will restore his legs if he gathers information about the Na'vi and the clan's gathering place, a giant tree called Hometree,[35] which stands above the richest deposit of unobtanium in the area. When Grace learns of this, she transfers herself, Jake, and Norm to an outpost. Over the following three months, Jake grows to sympathize with the natives. After Jake is initiated into the tribe, he and Neytiri choose each other as mates, and soon afterward, Jake reveals his change of allegiance when he attempts to disable a bulldozer that threatens to destroy a sacred Na'vi site. When Quaritch shows a video recording of Jake's attack on the bulldozer to Administrator Parker Selfridge,[36] and another in which Jake admits that the Na'vi will never abandon Hometree, Selfridge orders Hometree destroyed.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Lord of The Rings">
		<title>Lord of The Rings</title>
		<regie>Peter Jackson</regie>
		<year>2001</year>
		<url>resources/movies/lordOfTheRings1.jpg</url>
		<producer>Alan Lee</producer>
		<music>Howard Shore</music>
		<runtime>558</runtime>
		<plot>
			In the Second Age of Middle-earth, the lords of Elves, Dwarves, and Men are given Rings of Power. Unbeknownst to them, the Dark Lord Sauron forges the One Ring in Mount Doom, infusing into it a great part of his power to dominate, through it and at a distance, the other Rings, so he might conquer Middle-earth. A final alliance of men and elves battles Sauron's forces in Mordor, where Prince Isildur of Gondor severs Sauron's finger, and the Ring with it, thereby destroying his physical form. With Sauron's first defeat, the Third Age of Middle-earth begins. Unfortunately, the Ring's influence corrupts Isildur, and, rather than destroy the Ring, Isildur takes it for himself. Isildur is later killed by Orcs, and the Ring is lost for 2,500 years, until it is found by Gollum, who owns it for five centuries. The Ring is then found by a hobbit named Bilbo Baggins, who turns invisible when he puts it on, but is unaware of its history.
			Sixty years later, Bilbo celebrates his 111th birthday in the Shire, reuniting with his old friend, Gandalf the Grey. Bilbo reveals that he intends to leave the Shire for one last adventure, and he leaves his inheritance, including the Ring, to his nephew, Frodo. Although Bilbo has begun to become corrupted by the Ring and tries to keep it for himself, Gandalf intervenes. Gandalf, suspicious of the Ring, tells Frodo to keep it secret and to keep it safe. Gandalf then investigates the Ring, discovers its true nature, and returns to warn Frodo. Gandalf also learns that Gollum was tortured by Orcs, and that Gollum uttered two words during his torture: "Shire" and "Baggins." Gandalf instructs Frodo to leave the Shire, accompanied by his friend Samwise Gamgee. Gandalf rides to Isengard to meet with fellow wizard Saruman the White, but learns that he has joined forces with Sauron, who has dispatched his nine undead Nazgûl servants to find Frodo. After a brief battle, Saruman imprisons Gandalf.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Titanic">
		<title>Titanic</title>
		<regie>James Cameron</regie>
		<year>1997</year>
		<url>resources/movies/titanic.jpg</url>
		<producer>James Cameron</producer>
		<music>James Horner</music>
		<runtime>195</runtime>
		<plot>
			In 1996, treasure hunter Brock Lovett and his team board the research vessel Akademik Mstislav Keldysh to search the wreck of RMS Titanic for a necklace with a rare diamond, the Heart of the Ocean. They recover a safe containing a drawing of a young woman wearing only the necklace dated April 14, 1912, the day the ship struck the iceberg.[Note 1] Rose Dawson Calvert, the woman in the drawing, is brought aboard Keldysh and tells Lovett of her experiences aboard Titanic.
			In 1912 Southampton, 17-year-old first-class passenger Rose DeWitt Bukater, her fiancé Cal Hockley, and her mother Ruth board the luxurious Titanic. Ruth emphasizes that Rose's marriage will resolve their family's financial problems and allow them to retain their upper-class status. Distraught over the engagement, Rose climbs over the stern and contemplates suicide; Jack Dawson, a penniless artist, intervenes and discourages her. Discovered with Jack, Rose tells a concerned Cal that she was peering over the edge and Jack saved her from falling. When Cal becomes indifferent, she suggests to him that Jack deserves a reward. He invites Jack to dine with them in first-class the following night. Jack and Rose develop a tentative friendship, despite Cal and Ruth being wary of him. Following dinner, Rose secretly joins Jack at a party in third class.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<!-- Best Movies last Month -->
	<Movie id="Joker">
		<title>Joker</title>
		<regie>Todd Phillips</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/joker.jpg</url>
		<producer>Todd Phillips,Bradley Cooper</producer>
		<music>Hildur Guðnadóttir</music>
		<runtime>122</runtime>
		<plot>
			In 1981, party clown, social outsider and aspiring stand-up comedian Arthur Fleck lives with his mother, Penny, in Gotham City. Gotham's class society is rife with crime and unemployment, leaving segments of the population disenfranchised and impoverished. Arthur suffers from a medical disorder that causes him to laugh at inappropriate times, and depends on social services for medication. After a gang of delinquents attacks Arthur in an alley, his co-worker, Randall, gives him a gun for protection. Arthur invites his neighbor, single mother Sophie, to his stand-up comedy show, and they begin dating.
			While entertaining at a children's hospital, Arthur's gun falls out of his pocket. Randall lies that Arthur bought the gun himself and Arthur is fired. On the subway, still in his clown makeup, Arthur is beaten by three drunken Wayne Enterprises businessmen who were harassing a female passenger; he shoots two in self-defense and executes the third. The murders are condemned by billionaire mayoral candidate Thomas Wayne, who labels those envious of more successful people as "clowns". Demonstrations against Gotham's rich begin, with protesters donning clown masks in Arthur's image. Funding cuts shutter the social service program, leaving Arthur without medication.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Frozen 2">
		<title>Frozen 2</title>
		<regie>Jennifer Lee, Chris Buck</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/Frozen2.jpg</url>
		<producer>Peter Del Vecho</producer>
		<music>Robert Lopez, Kristen Anderson-Lopez, Christophe Beck</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			King Agnarr of Arendelle tells a story to his young children, Elsa and Anna, that their grandfather, King Runeard, established a treaty with the neighboring tribe of Northuldra by building a dam in their homeland, the Enchanted Forest. However, a fight
			occurs, resulting in Runeard's death. The battle enrages the elemental spirits of Earth, Fire, Water, and Air of the forest. The spirits disappear and a wall of mist traps everyone in the Enchanted Forest. Agnarr barely escapes due
			to the help of an unknown savior.
			<br />
			<br />
			Three years after her coronation, Elsa celebrates autumn in the kingdom with Anna, Olaf the snowman, Kristoff the ice harvester, and Kristoff's reindeer Sven. When
			Elsa hears a mysterious voice calling out to her, she follows it and unintentionally awakens the elemental spirits, who disrupt Arendelle, forcing everyone in the kingdom to evacuate. Grand Pabbie and the Trolls colony arrive at Arendelle
			and Pabbie informs that they must set things right by discovering the truth about the kingdom's past.
			<br />
			<br />
			Elsa, Anna, Olaf, Kristoff, and Sven embark to the Enchanted Forest, following the mysterious voice. After the mist
			parts at Elsa's touch, the air spirit, in the form of a tornado, appears and sweeps everyone in its vortex. Elsa stops it, forming a set of ice sculptures. The sisters discover the sculptures are images from their father's past and
			that their mother, Queen Iduna, was a Northuldra and was the one who had saved Agnarr. They encounter the Northuldra and a troop of Arendellian soldiers who are still in conflict with one another before the fire spirit appears. Elsa
			discovers the spirit to be an agitated magical salamander, and calms it down. Elsa and Anna arrange a truce between the soldiers and the Northuldra by explaining that their mother was Northuldran and their father was Arendellian. They
			later learn the existence of a fifth spirit who will unite people and the magic of nature.
			<br />
			<br />
			Elsa, Anna and Olaf continue to head north, leaving Kristoff and Sven behind. They find their parents' wrecked ship and a map with
			a route to Ahtohallan, a mythical river told by their mother to contain all explanations of the past. Elsa sends Anna and Olaf away to safety and continues alone. She encounters and tames the Nøkk, the water spirit who guards the sea
			to Ahtohallan. Reaching Ahtohallan, Elsa discovers that the voice calling to her was Iduna; that her powers were gifted by nature because of Iduna's selfless act of saving Agnarr; and that Elsa herself is the fifth spirit.
			<br />
			<br />
			Elsa then learns that the dam was built as a ruse to reduce the Northuldra's resources because of King Runeard's dislike of the tribe's connection with magic and intention to incorporate the region into his kingdom. She
			also learns he was the one who initiated the conflict by killing the leader of the Northuldra. Elsa sends this information to Anna before becoming frozen due to venturing into the most dangerous part of Ahtohallan. This in turn causes
			Olaf to fade away.
			<br />
			<br />
			Anna receives Elsa's message and concludes that the dam must be destroyed for peace to be restored. Anna finds and awakens the gigantic earth spirits and lures them towards the dam. The giants hurl boulders
			aimed at Anna which destroy the dam, sending a flood down the fjord to the kingdom. Elsa thaws out and returns to Arendelle, diverting the flood and saving the kingdom.
			<br />
			<br />
			As the wall of mist disappears, Elsa reunites with
			Anna and revives Olaf. Kristoff asks Anna to marry him and she accepts. Elsa explains that she and Anna are now the bridge between the people and the magical spirits. Anna becomes the new Queen of Arendelle, while Elsa becomes the
			protector of the Enchanted Forest, who regularly visits Arendelle as peace has been restored.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="The Adams Family">
		<title>The Adams Family</title>
		<regie>Conrad Vernon, Greg Tiernan</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/adamsfamily.jpg</url>
		<producer>Gail Berman</producer>
		<music>Mychael Danna</music>
		<runtime>87</runtime>
		<plot>
			Gomez and Morticia Addams are chased away with the rest of the Addams clan during their wedding ceremony by an angry mob that disapproves of their macabre nature. Grandmama buys Uncle Fester time to evacuate Gomez, Morticia, and Thing. Gomez and Morticia decide to move to New Jersey, a place "no one would be caught dead in." There, Gomez, Morticia, and Thing find their "perfect" home in an abandoned asylum on a hill. They meet Lurch, an escaped mental patient whom they hit when Thing was distracted driving the car, and immediately recruit him as their butler.
			Thirteen years later, the Addams family continue to live their gloomy lives in isolation from the outside world. Gomez prepares his son Pugsley for his upcoming Mazurka, a rite of passage that every Addams family member takes. Morticia struggles to keep their daughter, Wednesday, from wanting to experience the world outside of the mansion after a balloon and confetti appear on their property, as the fog surrounding it begins to lift.
			Elsewhere, reality TV host Margaux Needler, who is building a perfect planned community called "Assimilation" so her show will have a successful season finale, discovers the Addams family's household and becomes determined to rid the town of it when the family refuses to change. Wednesday then meets Margaux's neglected daughter Parker and convinces Morticia to let her attend junior high school. Pugsley struggles with the complicated traditions and pressure of his Mazurka, even with the guidance of Gomez and Uncle Fester. Grandmama arrives at the house for the event.
			At school, Wednesday defends Parker and her twin friends Layla and Kayla from the school bully named Bethany and befriends them after she resurrects some dead frogs and commands them to attack Bethany. Later on, the two discuss their frustrations and change their dressing habits – Parker becomes more gothic and Wednesday dresses more colorfully – to the shock of both of their mothers. After an argument with Morticia, Wednesday decides to run away in secret and stay with Parker for a while, which Pugsley inadvertently tells Morticia.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Last Christmas">
		<title>Last Christmas</title>
		<regie>Paul Feig</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/lastChristmas.jpg</url>
		<producer>Jessie Henderson</producer>
		<music>Theodore Shapiro</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			Katarina "Kate" works a dead end job as an elf at a Christmas shop in Central London, which sells ornaments all year round. She is homeless after being thrown out by her flatmate. While at work she notices a man outside staring upwards. She talks with him, learning that his name is Tom.
			After an unsuccessful singing audition, Kate sees Tom again and they go for a walk, where he charms her with his bizarre observations of London. The following morning, she discovers that her failure to lock the shop has led to a break-in. Her boss, who she refers to as "Santa", expresses disappointment in Kate, saying that she has changed from the charismatic and friendly person she used to be.
			Isolating herself from her last friend, Kate is forced to return to her parents' home. Yugoslavian immigrants, her mother, Petra, suffers from depression and her father, a former lawyer, works as a minicab driver as he can't afford to retrain to practice in the UK. Kate hates her mother, who dotes on her while ignoring Kate's sister Marta, a successful lawyer.
			Kate begins spending more time with Tom, who rides a bike and volunteers at a homeless shelter, which she initially critiques. Looking for Tom, who says he keeps his phone in a cupboard and often disappears for days at a time, she begins helping at the shelter in the hope of running into him but finds that the staff have never met him.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Zombieland 2">
		<title>Zombieland 2</title>
		<regie>Ruben Fleischer</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/Zombieland.jpg</url>
		<producer>Ruben Fleischer</producer>
		<music>David Sardy</music>
		<runtime>88</runtime>
		<plot>
			Two months have passed since a strain of mad cow disease mutated into "mad person disease" that became "mad zombie disease", which overran the entire United States (with the infection presumably spreading to the rest of the world), turning many Americans into vicious zombies. Survivors of the zombie epidemic have learned that growing attached to other survivors is not advisable because they could die at any moment, so many have taken to using their city of origin as nicknames.
			Unaffected college student Columbus (Jesse Eisenberg) is making his way from his college dorm in Austin, Texas, to Columbus, Ohio, to see whether his parents are still alive. He encounters Tallahassee (Woody Harrelson), another survivor, who is particularly violent in killing zombies. Though he does not appear to be sociable, Tallahassee reluctantly allows Columbus to travel with him. Tallahassee mentions he misses his puppy, "Buck" that was killed by zombies, as well as his affinity for Twinkies, which he actively tries to find.
			The pair meets Wichita (Emma Stone) and her younger sister Little Rock (Abigail Breslin) in a grocery store. The sisters are con artists, and trick Tallahassee and Columbus into handing over their weapons by pretending that Little Rock is infected by the disease, then stealing their Escalade. The two men find a yellow Hummer H2 loaded with weapons and go after the sisters. However, the girls spring another trap for them and take them hostage. Tallahassee steals his gun back and has a stand-off with Wichita, until Columbus lashes out in anger saying that they have bigger problems to worry about, resulting in an uneasy truce between them.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<!-- all other movies -->
	<Movie id="Jumanji - Next Level">
		<title>Jumanji - Next Level</title>
		<regie>Dwayne Johnson</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/jumanjiNext.jpg</url>
		<producer>Dwayne Johnson</producer>
		<music>Henry Jackman</music>
		<runtime>123</runtime>
		<plot>
			Three years after the events of the previous film, Spencer, Fridge, Martha, and Bethany have gone their separate ways but make plans to meet up in Brantford. However, Spencer is apprehensive about meeting up with everyone, especially Martha whom he put his relationship with on hold, due to thinking they have better lives. On his first night there, he realizes that his time within Jumanji was what made him feel relevant and sets out to return.
			The next day, Fridge, Martha, and Bethany become concerned when Spencer fails to show up. Heading to his house, they meet Spencer's grandfather Eddie, who's staying at the house while recovering from hip surgery, and his former friend Milo Walker. While there, the group discover that Spencer deliberately kept the broken pieces of the Jumanji game and resolve to go in and get him, but the malfunctioning game sucks in only Fridge and Martha, along with Eddie and Milo, forcing Bethany to reach out to fellow Jumanji player Alex Vreeke to help get in.
			In the game, Martha finds she's back in the Ruby Roundhouse avatar, but Fridge winds up in Professor Oberon's form while Eddie and Milo get Bravestone and Mouse respectively. After Fridge gets eaten by a python, costing him his first life, NPC guide Nigel Billingsley informs them the game has changed: a warlord named Jurgen the Brutal, who in this game is responsible for the deaths of Bravestone's parents, recently stole a magic necklace called the Falcon's Heart. As its magic provides fertility to the land so long as it stays in the sun, a drought struck the land when Jurgen stole the jewel. They must retrieve it before he sells it to a crime syndicate so both groups can combine, and show it to the sun in order to end the drought and save Jumanji.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Star Wars 9">
		<title>Star Wars 9</title>
		<regie>Kathleen Kennedy</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/starWars9.jpg</url>
		<producer>Kathleen Kennedy</producer>
		<music>John Williams</music>
		<runtime>142</runtime>
		<plot>
			Shortly after the destruction of Starkiller Base, General Leia Organa leads the evacuation of Resistance forces from D'Qar, when a First Order fleet arrives. Against Leia's orders, Poe Dameron leads a costly counterattack that destroys a First Order dreadnought. The remaining Resistance escapes into hyperspace, but the First Order uses a device to track them, and attacks again. Kylo Ren hesitates to fire on the lead Resistance ship after sensing his mother Leia's presence, but his wingmen destroy the bridge, killing most of the Resistance's leaders. Leia is dragged into space, but survives by using the Force. While Leia recovers, Vice Admiral Amilyn Holdo assumes command of the Resistance. Running low on fuel, the remaining fleet is pursued by the First Order.
			Rey, having traveled to Ahch-To with Chewbacca and R2-D2 aboard the Millennium Falcon, attempts to recruit Luke Skywalker to the Resistance. Under self-imposed exile, Luke refuses to help and says that the Jedi should end; but, encouraged by R2-D2, he eventually begins to teach Rey about the Force. Rey and Kylo begin communicating through the Force, puzzling them both. After Kylo tells Rey what happened between him and Luke that caused him to choose the dark side, Luke confesses that he momentarily contemplated killing Kylo upon sensing that Snoke was corrupting him; this prompted Kylo to destroy Luke's new Jedi Order. Convinced that Kylo can be redeemed, Rey leaves Ahch-To. Luke prepares to burn the Jedi library, but hesitates. Luke's teacher Yoda appears as a spirit, destroys the library by summoning a bolt of lightning, and encourages Luke to learn from his failure.
			Meanwhile, Poe entrusts Finn, mechanic Rose Tico, and BB-8 with a secret mission to find someone who can deactivate the First Order's tracking device, whom Maz Kanata says they can find in the casino town of Canto Bight. They meet the hacker DJ, and escape the city with the help of some stablehand children and riding animals they set free. Finn, Rose, and DJ infiltrate Snoke's ship, arriving at the same time as Rey, but are captured by Captain Phasma. Meanwhile, Kylo brings Rey to Snoke, who says that he facilitated the connection between her and Kylo as part of a plan to defeat Luke.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Star Wars 8">
		<title>Star Wars 8</title>
		<regie>Kathleen Kennedy</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/starWars8.jpg</url>
		<producer>Kathleen Kennedy</producer>
		<music>John Williams</music>
		<runtime>152</runtime>
		<plot>
			Shortly after the destruction of Starkiller Base, General Leia Organa leads the evacuation of Resistance forces from D'Qar, when a First Order fleet arrives. Against Leia's orders, Poe Dameron leads a costly counterattack that destroys a First Order dreadnought. The remaining Resistance escapes into hyperspace, but the First Order uses a device to track them, and attacks again. Kylo Ren hesitates to fire on the lead Resistance ship after sensing his mother Leia's presence, but his wingmen destroy the bridge, killing most of the Resistance's leaders. Leia is dragged into space, but survives by using the Force. While Leia recovers, Vice Admiral Amilyn Holdo assumes command of the Resistance. Running low on fuel, the remaining fleet is pursued by the First Order.
			Rey, having traveled to Ahch-To with Chewbacca and R2-D2 aboard the Millennium Falcon, attempts to recruit Luke Skywalker to the Resistance. Under self-imposed exile, Luke refuses to help and says that the Jedi should end; but, encouraged by R2-D2, he eventually begins to teach Rey about the Force. Rey and Kylo begin communicating through the Force, puzzling them both. After Kylo tells Rey what happened between him and Luke that caused him to choose the dark side, Luke confesses that he momentarily contemplated killing Kylo upon sensing that Snoke was corrupting him; this prompted Kylo to destroy Luke's new Jedi Order. Convinced that Kylo can be redeemed, Rey leaves Ahch-To. Luke prepares to burn the Jedi library, but hesitates. Luke's teacher Yoda appears as a spirit, destroys the library by summoning a bolt of lightning, and encourages Luke to learn from his failure.
			Meanwhile, Poe entrusts Finn, mechanic Rose Tico, and BB-8 with a secret mission to find someone who can deactivate the First Order's tracking device, whom Maz Kanata says they can find in the casino town of Canto Bight. They meet the hacker DJ, and escape the city with the help of some stablehand children and riding animals they set free. Finn, Rose, and DJ infiltrate Snoke's ship, arriving at the same time as Rey, but are captured by Captain Phasma. Meanwhile, Kylo brings Rey to Snoke, who says that he facilitated the connection between her and Kylo as part of a plan to defeat Luke.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="James Bond">
		<title>James Bond</title>
		<regie>Ian Fleming</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/jamesBond.jpg</url>
		<producer>Ian Fleming</producer>
		<music>Station Break</music>
		<runtime>99</runtime>
		<plot>
			Ian Fleming created the fictional character of James Bond as the central figure for his works. Bond is an intelligence officer in the Secret Intelligence Service, commonly known as MI6. Bond is known by his code number, 007, and was a Royal Naval Reserve Commander. Fleming based his fictional creation on a number of individuals he came across during his time in the Naval Intelligence Division and 30 Assault Unit during the Second World War, admitting that Bond "was a compound of all the secret agents and commando types I met during the war".[2] Among those types were his brother, Peter, who had been involved in behind-the-lines operations in Norway and Greece during the war.[3] Aside from Fleming's brother, a number of others also provided some aspects of Bond's make up, including Conrad O'Brien-ffrench, Patrick Dalzel-Job and Bill "Biffy" Dunderdale.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Bad Boys">
		<title>Bad Boys</title>
		<regie>Don Simpson,Jerry Bruckheimer</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/badBoys.jpg</url>
		<producer>Don Simpson, Jerry Bruckheimer</producer>
		<music>Mark Mancina</music>
		<runtime>119</runtime>
		<plot>
			At the police station, Julie insists on talking only to Lowrey, who is away. Knowing she never met Lowrey, captain Conrad Howard (Joe Pantoliano) forces Burnett to impersonate Lowrey to talk to her. At her apartment, Burnett and Julie are attacked by one of Fouchet's henchmen, whom Burnett kills. When they rendezvous with Lowrey, Burnett and Lowrey have to impersonate each other, and they keep it up in Julie's presence.
			Looking through mugshots, Julie identifies Noah as one of the henchmen. The trio go to Club Hell, one of Noah's known hangouts. After being spotted, Burnett knocks Casper unconscious during a bathroom fight. Julie tries to kill Fouchet but Burnett stops her. In the ensuing car chase, Lowrey kills Noah. The three manage to get away, but are caught on camera by a news helicopter and later seen by Burnett's family.
			Lowrey and Burnett meet their old informant Jojo (Michael Imperioli) and learn about the location of the chemist who is cutting the stolen drugs. The three return to Lowrey's apartment, where Burnett's wife confronts them and accidentally reveals to Julie they have been impersonating each other. Fouchet's gang shows up and kidnaps Julie.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Birds Of Prey">
		<title>Birds Of Prey</title>
		<regie>Margot Robbie</regie>
		<year>February 7, 2020</year>
		<url>resources/movies/birdOfPrey.jpg</url>
		<producer>Margot Robbie</producer>
		<music>Daniel Pemberton</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			By July 2018, the film was entering pre-production. Robbie confirmed the film would be titled Birds of Prey, describing it as "different" from the other DC films featuring Harley Quinn, and said it would be produced on a relatively small budget compared to other superhero films.She also stated that Harley Quinn would receive a new costume, and teased the casting of diverse actors.The line-up for the Birds of Prey team was revealed to include Black Canary, Huntress, Cassandra Cain, and Renee Montoya, with the villain set to be a Batman adversary who had not yet been seen in film.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Black Widow">
		<title>Black Widow</title>
		<regie>Kevin Feige</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/blackWidow.jpg</url>
		<producer>Kevin Feige</producer>
		<music>Scarlett Johansson</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			In February 2014, Feige stated that after exploring Black Widow's past in Age of Ultron, he would like to see it explored further in a solo film, which already had development work done for it, including a "pretty in depth" treatment by Nicole Perlman, who co-wrote Marvel's Guardians of the Galaxy (2014). The following April, Johansson expressed interest in starring in a Black Widow film, and said that it would be driven by demand from the audience. That July, Hayter expressed interest in reviving the project for Marvel,[35] and the following month, director Neil Marshall stated that he "would love to do a Black Widow film," saying he felt the character was "really interesting she doesn't have any superpowers, she just has extraordinary skills, and the world that she comes from, being this ex-K.G.B. assassin, I find that really fascinating."[36] In April 2015, Johansson spoke more on the possibility of a solo Black Widow film, seeing the potential to explore the different "layers" of her depicted in the different films so far, but also stating that "right now I think this character is used well in this part of the universe". While promoting Captain America: Civil War the next April, Feige noted that due to the announced schedule of films, any potential Black Widow film would be four or five years away. He added that Marvel was "creatively and emotionally" committed to making a Black Widow film eventually.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="Cats">
		<title>Cats</title>
		<regie>Tom Hooper</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/cats.jpg</url>
		<producer>Tom Hooper</producer>
		<music>Andrew Lloyd Webber, Taylor Swift</music>
		<runtime>103</runtime>
		<plot>
			In June 2018, there were reports Anne Hathaway was considered for a role in the film, but she passed due to scheduling conflict. In July 2018, Jennifer Hudson, Taylor Swift, James Corden, and Ian McKellen joined the cast.[34] Swift had previously tested for the role of Éponine in Tom Hooper's Les Misérables but was given the part of Bombalurina without an audition.
			In September 2018, Laurie Davidson and Mette Towley were cast, with Steven Spielberg announced to be executive producing. In October 2018, Idris Elba and Judi Dench joined the cast of the film. Dench was cast in the original stage musical, but was forced to pull out due to a torn Achilles tendon; Lloyd Webber and Hooper decided to make Old Deuteronomy a woman and offered her the role.
			In November 2018, ballet dancers Francesca Hayward and Steven McRae as well as Rebel Wilson, Jason Derulo, and Robert Fairchild joined the cast of the film with rehearsals commencing at Leavesden Studios in Hertfordshire, England.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
	<Movie id="The Beauty and the Beast">
		<title>The Beauty and the Beast</title>
		<regie>Ruben Fleischer</regie>
		<year>2019</year>
		<url>resources/movies/beautyandthebeast.jpg</url>
		<producer>Bill Condon</producer>
		<music>Alan Menken</music>
		<runtime>129</runtime>
		<plot>
			A beautiful enchantress disguised as an old beggar woman arrives at a castle during a ball and offers the host, a cruel and selfish prince, a rose in return for shelter from a storm. When he refuses, she reveals her identity. To punish the prince for his lack of compassion, the enchantress transforms him into a beast and his servants into household objects, then erases the castle, the prince and his servants from the memories of their loved ones. She casts a spell on the rose and warns the prince that the curse will only be broken if he learns to love another, and earn their love in return, before the last petal falls, or he will remain a beast forever.
			Some years later, in the small town of Villeneuve, Belle, the book-loving daughter of an inventor Maurice, dreams of adventure and brushes off advances from Gaston, an arrogant former soldier. On his way to a convention and lost in the forest, Maurice seeks refuge in the Beast's castle, but the Beast imprisons him for stealing a rose from his garden as a gift to Belle. When Maurice's horse returns without him, Belle ventures out in search for him, and finds him locked in the castle dungeon. The Beast agrees to let her take Maurice's place.
		</plot>
	</Movie>
</library>
